Guide to the Voices Breaking Boundaries Records
University of Houston Libraries
- Finance and Funding
  - Grant Applications
    - Simmons Foundation, 2013-2015 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - St. Lukes Episcopal Health Charities, 2006-2009 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - TX Commission for the Arts, 2006-2007 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - TX Commission for the Arts - Arts Create, 2009-2010 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - TX Commission for the Arts - Arts Create, 2010-2011 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - TX Commission for the Arts - Arts Create, 2011-2012 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - TX Commission for the Arts - Arts Education, 2008-2009 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - TX Commission for the Arts - Arts Respond, 2010-2012 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - TX Commission for the Arts - Core Support, 2008-2009 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - TX Commission for the Arts - Core Support, 2011-2012 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - TCA Cultural Connections, 2005-2008 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - United Way, 2006, 2008, 2011 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Wortham, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Wortham, 2012-2013 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Writers League of Texas, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Other grants, 2000-2003 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Other grants, 2004-2007 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Other grants, 2008-2016 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Individual donations, 2000, 2005-2009, undated (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Blank donation forms, undated (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Financial Statements and Budgets
    - Budget notes and projections (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Fiscal Year 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Fiscal Year 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Fiscal Year 2003-2004 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Fiscal Year 2004-2005 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Fiscal Year 2005-2006 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Fiscal Year 2006-2007 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Fiscal Year 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Fiscal Year 2008-2009 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Fiscal Year 2009-2010 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Fiscal Year 2010-2011 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Fiscal Year 2011-2012 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Fiscal Year 2012-2013 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Fiscal Year 2013-2014 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Fiscal Year 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Ticket sales reports, 2003-2007 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Tax Information
    - Fiscal Years 2001-2003 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Fiscal Years 2004-2009 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Fiscal Years 2009-2011 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Undated tax information (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Partner Organizations
    - Aurora Picture Show, 2004, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Colleges and Universities, 2002, 2006, 2008-2009, undated (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Diverse Works, 2000-2009 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Dosti, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Film Festivals, 2005, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Fotofest, 2003-2007 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Golden Seahorse Productions, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - HISD, 2003, 2006-2009 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - KPFT, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - New Voices, 2008-2009 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Project Rowhouses, 2003-2005 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Youth Advocates, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Other partner organizations, 2003-2010 (Box 21, Folder 33)
- Receipts and Expenses
  This series contains documents confirming VBB expenses, including bills, receipts and bank documents.
  - Banking and Loans
    - Banking, 2002-2012, undated (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Loan reimbursements, 2003, 2005, 2007-2009 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Events and Marketing
    - Books and publishers, 2001, 2003, 2005-2009 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Event expenses, 2002-2015 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Fundraising (Paypal), 2008-2010 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Printing - Copy.com, 2001-2007 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Printing - Copy.com, 2007-2015 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Printing - Other printing and publishing, 2002-2015 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Web design and marketing, 2004-2005, 2008-2010, 2014 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Food and Drink
    - Food and drink - groceries, 2001-2015 (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Restaurants and catering, 2002-2008 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Restaurants and catering, 2009-2015, undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Human Resources Expenses
    - Education and professional development, 2007-2009, 2011 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Memberships, 2009-2010 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Professional services, 2008, 2011 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Insurance
    - General liability insurance, 2005, 2009-2010 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Health insurance, 2008, 2010 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Professional liability insurance, 2003-2007 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Professional liability insurance, 2008-2011 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Workman's compensation, 2009-2010 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Office Supplies
    - General supplies, 2001-2012, 2015, undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Mailing and shipping, 2001-2012, 2015, undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Technology, 2001-2011 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Phone Service
    - ATandT, 2006-2012 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - MCI, 2003-2006 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Sprint, 2000-2003 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Other phone service, 2002-2009 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Real Estate and Maintenance
    - Energy and utilities, 2010-2011 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Permits and maintenance, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Rent and real estate, 2003, 2006-2011 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Travel
    - Airfare, 2003-2010, 2014 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Fuel and parking, 2004-2011, 2015, undated (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Hotels, 2004-2010 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Unidentified expenses, 2003, 2007-2008, 2012, undated (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Audiovisual Media
  This series contains a variety of audiovisual materials related to VBB activities including; cassette tapes, VHS tapes, DV tapes, CDs and DVDs.
  - Cassette Tapes
    - Traveling Film South Asia, 2001 (Box 11, Item 1)
    - February 10, 2002 (Box 11, Item 2)
    - March 3, 2002 (Box 11, Item 3-4)
    - Al-Bustan June 27, 2002 (Box 11, Item 5)
    - VBB October 20, 2002 MFAH (Box 11, Item 6)
    - VBB reading and dance December 8, 2002 (Box 11, Item 7)
    - VBB readings open mic December 8, 2002 (Box 11, Item 8)
    - Class February 5, 2003 (Box 11, Item 9)
    - Class Furr Febrary 19-24, 2003 (Box 11, Item 10)
    - Furr February 24, 2003 (Box 11, Item 11)
    - Furr February 8, 2003 (Box 11, Item 12)
    - VBB March 13, 2003 (Box 11, Item 13)
    - Furr Jawad March 13, 2003 (Box 11, Item 14)
    - Furr Jawad March 6-14, 2003 (Box 11, Item 15)
    - VBB April 13, 2003 (Box 11, Item 16)
    - Ben interview April 13, 2003 (Box 11, Item 17)
    - Panel 1 MFA Filmfest May 17, 2003 (Box 11, Item 18)
    - Panel 2 MFA Filmfest May 17, 2003 (Box 11, Item 19)
    - Law High School Students March 2009 (Box 11, Item 20)
    - VBB Story, undated (Box 11, Item 21)
    - VBB Inprint, undated (Box 11, Item 22-23)
    - VBB Mainstreet, undated (Box 11, Item 24)
    - Translating Intimacy, undated (Box 11, Item 25)
    - VBB Sobhi al Zobaidi Crossing Kalandia November 21-22 (Box 11, Item 26)
    - Ben, undated (Box 11, Item 27)
    - Jasmine, undated (Box 11, Item 28)
    - Unlabeled Cassette, undated (Box 11, Item 29-34)
  - VHS Tapes
    - MFA Student Docents 2000 (Box 12, Item 1)
    - VBB September 10, 2000 (Box 12, Item 2)
    - VBB Jawad, Susan Howard, Lorenzo Thomas May 2001 (Box 12, Item 3)
    - VBB Traveling Film South Asia Opening Remarks, 2001 (Box 12, Item 4)
    - VBB Film South Asia Night #4, 2001 (Box 12, Item 5)
    - VBB at DW [DiverseWorks] May 19, 2002 (Box 12, Item 6)
    - Stories That Must Be Told Sharpstown June 2002 (Box 12, Item 7)
    - VBB Stories June 2002 (Box 12, Item 8)
    - War and Peace by Anand Patwardham, 2002 (Box 12, Item 9-10)
    - Dam/Age A Film with Arundhati Roy, 2002 (Box 12, Item 11)
    - Pakistan/Artery August 6, 2004 (Box 12, Item 12)
    - Margarita, undated (Box 12, Item 13)
    - Voices Breaking Boundaries, undated (Box 12, Item 14-15)
  - DV Tapes
    - DV Tapes (Box 13, Item 1)
    - Reel Stories, 2003 (Box 13, Item 2)
    - Beena, 2004 (Box 13, Item 3)
    - Minal, 2005 (Box 13, Item 4-5)
    - Charlie Maloy, 2007 (Box 13, Item 6)
    - Mangopir Lyon, 2007 (Box 13, Item 7)
    - Minal Khi, 2007 (Box 13, Item 8)
    - Minal Karachi, 2007 (Box 13, Item 9)
    - GEO footage 2007-2008 (Box 13, Item 10)
    - Gun Show, 2008 (Box 13, Item 11)
    - Karachi December 2008 (Box 13, Item 12)
    - Living Room Art, 2008 (Box 13, Item 13-15)
    - Minal Lee, 2008 (Box 13, Item 16)
    - Words For Peace, 2008 (Box 13, Item 17-19)
    - Houston Imran Aslam March 2009 (Box 13, Item 20)
    - Pakistan Live Broadcast, 2009 (Box 13, Item 21-29)
    - Planned Parenthood, 2009 (Box 13, Item 30)
    - PMA Reference Film D’Art, 2009 (Box 13, Item 31)
    - For Sehba Sarwar, October 2009 (Box 13, Item 32)
    - Yuneun East Meets East, 2009 (Box 13, Item 33)
    - Art Car Parade, 2010 (Box 13, Item 34)
    - Patti Smith, 2010 (Box 13, Item 35-37)
    - Sehba Interview Music Magic, 2010 (Box 13, Item 38)
    - Karachi Geet Interview, 2011 (Box 13, Item 39-40)
    - Khi December 2011 (Box 13, Item 41-42)
    - Living Room Art, 2011 (Box 13, Item 43)
    - Minal Musical Performance Rice, 2011 (Box 13, Item 44)
    - Other’s Love, 2011 (Box 13, Item 45-46)
    - Politiqueer, 2011 (Box 13, Item 47-48)
    - Sehba Interview, 2011 (Box 13, Item 49)
    - Anne Scott, 2012 (Box 13, Item 50)
    - David Barsamian, 2012 (Box 13, Item 51-52)
    - Freedman Town Interviews, 2012 (Box 13, Item 53)
    - Homes and Histories, 2012 (Box 13, Item 54-56)
    - Minal Class 2011-2012 (Box 13, Item 57)
    - Minal Class Spring 2012 (Box 13, Item 58)
    - Teachers Speak Out, 2012 (Box 13, Item 59-60)
    - La Valiente Fundraiser, 2012 (Box 13, Item 61-62)
    - What is Color, 2012 (Box 13, Item 63-64)
    - LRA [Living Room Art] Women Under Siege, 2012 (Box 13, Item 65-68)
    - Sehba Interview Women Under Siege, 2013 (Box 13, Item 69)
    - Homes and Histories, 2013 (Box 13, Item 70-71)
    - Sehba Interview, 2013 (Box 13, Item 72)
    - VBB - Struggles, 2013 (Box 13, Item 73-75)
    - VBB - La Valiente Fundraiser, 2013 (Box 13, Item 76)
    - We the People, 2016 (Box 13, Item 77-78)
    - Aslam Cultural Narr March 29 (Box 13, Item 79)
    - Alice Valdez Interview, undated (Box 13, Item 80)
    - Anand Paturalla Q and A session, undated (Box 13, Item 81)
    - Bustamente, undated (Box 13, Item 82-83)
    - Gun Show Pascal, undated (Box 13, Item 84)
    - Hammering, undated (Box 13, Item 85)
    - Interview with Sehba and Miriam Kass, undated (Box 13, Item 86)
    - Marc, undated (Box 13, Item 87-88)
    - Minal Narrative August 27 (Box 13, Item 89)
    - Minal, undated (Box 13, Item 90)
    - Dr. Mungi PMA Ref TV St, undated (Box 13, Item 91)
    - VBB Tape, undated (Box 13, Item 92)
    - Zakia Dawn Interview, undated (Box 13, Item 93)
    - Unlabeled DV Tape, undated (Box 13, Item 94-104)
- Digital Media
  - First hard drive transfer from Sehba's computer and external hard drive, approximately 2000-2013
    Folder names reflect original organization and naming. Materials include primarily digital photographs, fliers, and production files. Some fliers that were eventually produced may be duplicated in the print collection. Files were transffered from both Sehba Sarwar's laptop and an external hard drive on September 24, 2015. Files saved at 2014-015_002_vbb. 16.6GB (approximately 18,273 files).
    - Arts Education (Folder 1)
    - Arts Production (Folder 2)
    - Marketing (Folder 3)
    - Marketing 2 (Folder 4)
    - Media / Press (Folder 5)
    - Non-profit (Folder 6)
    - VBB Pictures (Folder 7)
    - Website / video stuff (Folder 8)
  - Second hard drive transfer from Sehba's computer
    Folder names reflect original organization and naming. Files transffered on October 14, 2016. Files saved at 2014-015_005_vbb. 26.1GB (approximately 6,568 files).
    - 2015-16 Marketing (Folder 1)
    - 2016 conferences (Folder 2)
    - 2016-04-02 Rothko Chapel (Folder 3)
    - 2016-04-19 Brazos Bookstore (Folder 4)
    - 2016-06-25 Borderlines (Folder 5)
    - 2016-06-25 LRA (Folder 6)
    - Non-profit (Folder 7)
    - Photographs (Folder 8)
    - Strategic Plan (Folder 9)
    - VBB Posters (Folder 10)
    - Website / Video Stuff (Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous files (Folder 12)
  - Third hard drive transfer from Sehba's Mac hard drive
    This digital accession is not yet processed and may not be available for research.
  - Media on Discs
    - Data Compact Discs
      - Sehba, Images (Compact disc 1)
      - Nusrat Pics 02 VBB 08 Dec 02 (Compact disc 2)
      - La Voz VBB, March 2003 (Compact disc 3)
      - More pictures VBB FURR Amalgamation, 2003 (Compact disc 4)
      - FLOWPICS (Compact disc 5)
      - Class Pics Sehba (Compact disc 6)
      - Translating Intimacy (Compact disc 7)
      - Thomas VBB (Compact disc 8)
      - VBB Stuff for Nuscat, 2001-2002 (Compact disc 9)
      - Sehba olive trees... (Compact disc 10)
      - Project Row Houses Juneteenth Eldorado Postcard 6/2/04 (Compact disc 11)
      - The Listening Place @PRH - supporting docs (Compact disc 12)
      - Project Row Houses Audio Training + Storytelling Series Documents (Compact disc 13)
      - Lvg Art 12 24 04, Part I, Public Art (Compact disc 14)
      - More VBB pics board mtg Furr 11-9-03 (Compact disc 15)
      - To Sebah 10 tracs (Compact disc 16)
      - VBB pics (Compact disc 17)
      - VBB Words for Peace Card, Design by Oskar Sonnen (Compact disc 18)
      - VBB brochure (Compact disc 19)
      - Spam Photos (Compact disc 20)
      - "Stories" Summer 2003 flyer (Compact disc 21)
      - VBB Pics 2003 Isaias (Compact disc 22)
      - VBB Pictures (Compact disc 23)
      - Celebrating Cubanos Nov 2002 (Compact disc 24)
      - VBB 2003-04 Designs (3) (Compact disc 25)
      - VBB "Stories" images (Compact disc 26)
      - VBB Fund Dinner, Words for Peace, 2006 (Compact disc 27)
      - w4p3-2004-08-18 (Compact disc 28)
      - VBB, W4P2 Cross/Currents, 9/20-21/2003, Email, Postcard, Poster (Compact disc 29)
      - Photos, David Barsamian At The Station, June 15, 12; Photo Credit Wally James (Compact disc 30)
      - Quickbook Backup Program (Compact disc 31)
      - Drik, Powerpoint and Audio (Compact disc 32)
      - BX Pics (Compact disc 33)
      - SPAM (Compact disc 34)
      - Lee HS (Compact disc 35)
      - Retelling Histories, VBB (Compact disc 36)
      - backup, burn vbb (Compact disc 37)
      - VBB Backup (Compact disc 38)
      - VBB Edu Photos (Compact disc 39)
      - Sebha @ CLMP '08 (Compact disc 40)
      - EELA 1-30-11, VBB, Color - Photos by E. Hester (Compact disc 41)
      - Tehrike-e Niswan, Photos (Compact disc 42)
      - Flood Relief Images w/Docx Files (Compact disc 43)
      - Honoring Dissent/Descent, images (Compact disc 44)
      - East End Live Art Annual La Voz Feminina 7, March 28, 2010, Burnell McCray Photographer (Compact disc 45)
      - QSS_CD (Compact disc 46-47)
      - Old Files, 00-03 (Compact disc 48)
      - Oskar's VBB Archive (Compact disc 49)
      - VBB images for Michael Woodson (Compact disc 50)
      - Various Pics, VBB Open House, 2004 (Compact disc 51)
      - DeSeto 713/705-1470, VBB 10th Select (Compact disc 52)
      - House Exhbit, DeSoto, Voices Breaking Boundaries (Compact disc 53)
      - La Voz Feminina 4, Images (Compact disc 54)
      - 2007 Houston Palestine Film Festival CD#1: May 11-13, Photos by: Iman Saqr (Compact disc 55)
      - VBB 2005 (Compact disc 56)
      - Antaeus Bio (Compact disc 57)
      - VBB 2003-04 Designs (1) (Compact disc 58)
      - VBB (Compact disc 59)
      - Guantanamo Images (Compact disc 60)
      - VBB "Area K" Flyer (Compact disc 61)
      - VBB 2003-04 Designs (2) (Compact disc 62)
      - VBB March 27 (Compact disc 63)
      - Living Room Art - Art Car Crawl, In The First Ward, 5-1-2010, Burnell McCray Photographer (Compact disc 64)
      - TRUCK ART, ABRO (Compact disc 65)
      - ABRO TRUCK ART, March 2010 (Compact disc 66)
      - LRA Hester, 10/22/11 (Compact disc 67)
      - VBB Third Ward - Karachi Part 1, 10-22-11, Burnell McCray Photographer (Compact disc 68)
      - East End Live Art - Artists and Mothers, Photographer Burnell McCray, 5-10-09 (Compact disc 69)
      - VBB Words 4 Peace 5 March 30 2008 (Compact disc 70)
      - VBB - Other Loves, Celebrating Queer Artists, 6-5-11, Burnell McCray Photographer (Compact disc 71)
      - VBB- Revisting the First Ward, Exploring Local Boundaries, 5-7-11, Burnell McCray Photographer (Compact disc 72)
      - VBB - Teacherss and Students Speak Out 3, 4-17-11, Burnell McCray Photographer (Compact disc 73)
      - Art Car Sprawl, 5/1/10, Photos by Burnell McCray (Compact disc 74)
      - VBB Wat Color Got To Do With It? Show Photos, Interracial Relationiships, 1-30-11, Burnell McCray Photographer (Compact disc 75)
      - VBB Honoring Dissent/Descent, 11.7.09, E Hester (Compact disc 76)
      - Intimate Dinner for Patti Smith, 4-18-2010, Burnell McCray Photographer (Compact disc 77)
      - Teachers Speak Out 2, 4-18-2010, VBB-East End Live Art, Burnell McCray Photographer (Compact disc 78)
      - Just Kids - Patti Smith Photos, U of H-VBB, 4-19-2010, Burnell McCray Photographer (Compact disc 79)
      - Voices Breaking Boundaries, East End Live Art, Un/Natural Disasters, May 23, 2010, Burnell McCray Photographer (Compact disc 80)
      - Pakistan Floor Relief Fundraiser, 9-19-2010, Burnell McCray Photographer (Compact disc 81)
      - Video Clip Flood (Compact disc 82)
      - House Exhibit,VBB, DeSoto (Compact disc 83)
      - VBB Living Room Art Production, Women Voices in Sixth Ward, Disk 1 of 2, 11-6-10, Burnell McCray Photographer (Compact disc 84)
      - VBB Living Room Art Production, Women Voices in Sixth Ward, Disk 2 of 2, 11-6-10, Burnell McCray Photographer (Compact disc 85)
      - WAF Pictures (Compact disc 86)
      - VBB, Amalgamation: Hear what teenagers have to say...June 27, 2003, Photos by Paul Hester (Compact disc 87)
      - VBB Pics, 2000-2001 (Compact disc 88)
      - VBB#2, 2001-2004 (Compact disc 89)
      - VBB#3, 03-05 (Compact disc 90)
      - VBB, Living Room Art Show, Oskar S. and Danny K. (Compact disc 91)
      - East End Live Art, Is This Change? 12-14-08, Pics by Eric Hester (Compact disc 92)
      - VBB Photos (Compact disc 93)
      - Pics by Eric, Art Car, VBB (Compact disc 94)
      - Patti Smith Radio Interview Photos, 4-19-2010, Burnell McCray Photographer (Compact disc 95)
      - EQ Movie (Compact disc 96)
      - VBB Accounting by Stephanie Atwood (Compact disc 97)
      - Words for Peace, Images 1-98, Woodson (Compact disc 98)
      - Words for Peace, Images 99-200, Woodson (Compact disc 99)
      - Film, Food and VBB on the World Wide Web - 7pm - Saturday 20 October 2012, Photographer Burnell McCray (Compact disc 100)
      - Voices Breaking Boundaries, 2009-2010 Season, Files and Sehba Sarwar, Website Files and Photos, From A. R. Martinez (Compact disc 101)
      - VBB Presents Cultural Narrative: Imran Aslam, 3/29/09, Station Museum (Compact disc 102)
      - East End Live Art: Artists/Mothers, VBB, 5-10-09, Burnell McCray Photographer (Compact disc 103)
      - VBB Event - Teachers Speak Out, East End Live Art, 4-19-09 and Cultural Narratives, 3/09 (Compact disc 104)
      - PP Protest Pictures (Compact disc 105)
    - Audio Compact Discs
      - Howard Zinn, Words 4 Peace 4 (Audio cd 1)
      - Valiente Music (Audio cd 2-7)
      - LA Revv 2 2003 (Audio cd 8)
      - Michael Woodson, 8 Pieces (Audio cd 9)
      - Michael Woodson in Thirteen Pieces (Audio cd 10)
      - Chalmers Johnson, Blowback: Impacts of the New Millenium, Seattle, WA, 11 Feb 2004 (Audio cd 11)
      - Arundhati Roy, Public Power in the Age of Empire, San Francisco, CA, 16 Aug 2004 (Audio cd 12)
      - As'ad AbuKhalil, The Battle for Saudi Arabia, Berkeley, WA, 19 Aug 2004 (Audio cd 13)
      - Howard Zinn, Resistance and the Role of Artists, Cambridge, MA, 6 Feb 2004 (Audio cd 14)
      - Patti Smith - Interview April 19, 2010 (Audio cd 15)
      - Sound footage, Sehwan (Audio cd 16)
      - Sehba Sarwar Interview, Part 1, 9:24 KPFT studio Hou TX, Seb and Haniya, Oct 4, 2012 (Audio cd 17)
      - Sehba Sarwar Interview, Part 2, 11:00, Zeb and Haniya, recorded Oct 4, 2012 (Audio cd 18)
      - LA Revu 1, 2003 (Audio cd 19)
      - LA Revu 3, 2003 (Audio cd 20)
      - Boxhead Ensemble (Audio cd 21)
      - Living Art, 10 14 03, For Sehba (Audio cd 22)
      - RAM4, Madigra, The Greatest Hits (Audio cd 23)
      - RAM (Audio cd 24)
      - Audio Interview, Meet Janis and Cleola by Yunuen Perez Vertti, April, 2010 (Audio cd 25)
      - Denea Stewart, VBB, Icemaps (Audio cd 26)
      - Patti Smith on Living Art, for Sehba and VBB, 65:47, March 28, 2003 (Audio cd 27)
      - Patti Smith, 3:05 Min Clip, Liviging Art w/ Sehba and Mike(?) March 28, 2003 (Audio cd 28)
      - Tariq Ali, Imperial Hubris, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia 16 Dec 2005 (Audio cd 29)
      - Sehba - on Living Art, 1-28-05 (Audio cd 30)
      - VBB (Audio cd 31)
      - Best of Living Art (Audio cd 32)
      - Donnie Darko (Audio cd 33)
      - Voices Houston, Edited Verson (sic), #1 (Audio cd 34)
      - Voices Houston, Edited Verson (sic), #2 (Audio cd 35)
      - feedback (Audio cd 36)
      - PR - intv #1 (Audio cd 37)
    - DVDs
      - Voices Breaking Boundaries Spring SPAM 2007 (Dvd 1)
      - VBB Promo (Dvd 2-5)
      - VBB Promo Video (Dvd 6-8)
      - VBB Promotional Video (Dvd 9)
      - VBB excerpts Faroukh Virani (Dvd 10-13)
      - Vbb-3 (Dvd 14)
      - VBB excerpts Faroukh Virani (Dvd 15)
      - Vbb Spam 07-1 (Dvd 16)
      - VBB SPAM Summer 2007 (Dvd 17-18)
      - VBB: W4P4, Faroukh Virani (Dvd 19)
      - W4P4 (DVD), 8/30/07 F.V. (Dvd 20)
      - VBB @ Wesley Community Center, 2007 (Dvd 21)
      - The Palestine Tapes, by Jeff Stewart, 2007 (Dvd 22-23)
      - East meets West, VBB, Mix video, Living Room Art, Nov 7, 2009 (Dvd 24-25)
      - Abijon, Jump (Dvd 26)
      - VBB, Website Stuff (Dvd 27)
      - Oct 20, LRR Photos, Slideshow (Dvd 28)
      - VBB - Oct 20, LRA Documentaries, Looped (Dvd 29)
      - Fotos, Diciembre 2, 2012 (Dvd 30)
      - VBB Cultured Cocktails (Dvd 31)
      - Borderlines 2013 - 2014 2-1 (Dvd 32)
      - DVD for Nov 5; Outside DVD - Erick Slide Show 0 Yunuen Video (Dvd 33)
      - Theyarekilling-1 (Dvd 34)
      - Narrative2-1 (Dvd 35)
      - DVD for Nov 5 LRA Show; LRA October 22 Narratives Part 1 5-9 (Dvd 36)
      - DVD Nov 5 LRA Show; LRA October 22 Narratives Part 1 1-4 (Dvd 37)
      - 6th Ward Videos by Larissa Lindsay, loop (Dvd 38)
      - I am a woman (Dvd 39)
      - VBB (Dvd 41)
      - WAF Film, Aisha Godzar, 7:30 min (Dvd 40)
      - "MAA Poem" (1st) 3-12-12-11 (Dvd 42)
      - From Our Interior, 10-22-11, S. Sarwar (Dvd 43)
      - VBB Documentary, 2011 (Dvd 44)
      - VBB Doc 2011, Region (Dvd 45)
      - VBB - Documentary, 2011 by Farouk (Dvd 46)
      - VBB - Oct 20, LRA Documentaries Looped (Dvd 47)
      - T2F 12-23-11 (Dvd 48)
      - VBB, Words for Peace, 3-30-08, Photos by Eric Hester (Dvd 49)
      - Readings from Voices of a People's History of the United States, By Howard Zinn and Anthony Arnove (Dvd 50)
      - WFP4 99% (Dvd 51)
      - Homes and Histories documentary (Dvd 52)
      - Babette (Dvd 53)
      - Sufism - Tazeen, Protecting Space, Play (Dvd 54)
      - Patti Smith, DVD w/Menu, For Duplication, Original (Dvd 55)
      - VBB Brochure, 2010 (Dvd 56)
      - Jibran (Dvd 57)
      - Women Under Siege, Documentary Rough Cut, May 2012 (Dvd 58)
      - Qualls Images (Dvd 59)
      - WAF Film by Aisha Gadzar (Dvd 60)
      - Lee HS Spam, Spring 2007, VBB (Dvd 61)
      - 1. Montage, 2. Intro - Forgotten, 3. Update (Dvd 62)
      - 1. Overview, 2. Dialogue (Dvd 63)
      - VBB, Oskar Backup and Courtney's Card (Dvd 64)
      - VBB Spam 07 (Dvd 65)
      - VBB Promotional Video (Dvd 66-67)
      - Oskar - VBB, 2004-05: 2007-08 (Dvd 68)